Guide to the Samuel J. Tilden papers, 1794-1886 [bulk 1835-1876]
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series I. Correspondence, 1810 - 1919, n.d.; 38247; 35 boxes, 14.5 linear feet
  - I. B. General, 1830 - 1919, n.d.; 38280
    - Arnold & Company, 1877 - 1878; 38309 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Arnut, John, 1866 - 1872; 38310 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Ashley, Ossian Doolittle, 1886; 38311 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Averill, Horatio, 1862; 38312 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Avery, J. T., 1830; 38313 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Ayer, Harriet Hubbard, 1883; 38314 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Babcock, N., 1846; 38315 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Bache, Franklin, 1841; 38316 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Bacon, Daniel P., 1830, 1832; 38317 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Bacon, Marshal J., 1838 - 1839; 38318 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Bagley, John J., 1875; 38319 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Baiber, J., 1856; 38320 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Bailey, E. Prentiss, 1874; 38321 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Baker, George C., 1866; 38322 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Baldwin, George V. N., 1879; 38323 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Bancroft, George, 1864 - 1869, 1881 - 1886; 38324 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Bangs, N.D., 1871 - 1875; 38325 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Bar Association of Albany, 1868; 38326 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Bar Association of New York City, 1876; 38327 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Barbour, John M., 1841, 1861, 1876; 38328 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Baring, Thomas, 1884; 38329 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Barlow, Francis C., 1871 - 1876, 1886; 38330 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Barlow, S. L. M. (Samuel Latham Mitchill), 1860 - 1879; 38331 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Barnard, Frederick A. P., 1874; 38332 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Barnes, George T., 1880; 38334 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Barnes, William Henry Linow, 1861; 38335 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Barney, Hiram, 1861, 1875 - 1876; 38336 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Barnum, Henry A., 1858, 1865 - 1886, n.d; 38337 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Barr, James P., 1879; 38338 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Barrow, Eustace, 1864; 38339 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Bartlett, Joseph J., 1874; 38340 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Bartlett, William O., 1878 - 1881; 38341 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Bass, George W., 1877; 38342 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Bates, B., 1846; 38343 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Bates, J. F., 1878; 38344 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Bauer, Charles Henry, 1876; 38345 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Bayard, Thomas F., 1871, 1876; 38346 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Baylor, R., 1875; 38347 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Beach, Allen C., 1868 - 1879; 38348 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Beach, William C., 1875; 38349 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Beardsley, A.M., 1845; 38350 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Beardsley, C.S., 1882; 38351 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Bech, Friedrich, undated; 38352 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Bedford, Gunning J., 1872 - 1884, n.d.; 38353 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Bedient, J. J., ca. 1839; 38354 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Bedle, Joseph Dorsett, 1876 - 1877; 38355 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Beebe, G. M., 1870, 1872, 1875; 38356 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Beekman, J. P. (John Pruyn), 1848 - 1857; 38357 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Beerling, August, 1886; 38358 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bell (first name unknown), 1880; 38359 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Belmont, Alva Vanderbilt, 1883; 38360 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Belmont, August, 1860 - 1877; 38361 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Belmont, Perry, 1875; 38362 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Bennett, J. G., 1876; 38363 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Benton, C. G., 1848 - 1886; 38364 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Bergen, A. J., 1846; 38365 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Bergen, Frank, 1885; 38366 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Bergh, Henry, 1875 - 1879; 38367 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Bernhardt, Sarah, 1880; 38368 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Biddle, Clement C., 1841; 38369 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Biddle, George W., 1887; 38370 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Bieber, Walt, 1879; 38371 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Bigelow, Horatio, 1864; 38372 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Bigelow, John, 1846 - 1876; 1879 - 1886, n.d; 38373 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Bigelow, Poultney, 1881 - 1883; 38374 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Bigler, William, 1864 - 1868, 1875 - 1877; 38375 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Bingham, H.H., 1872; 38376 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      See also: Glenn W. Schofield.
    - Birdsall, Ausburn, 1874, 1876; 38377 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Bishop, George, 1862; 38378 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Bishop, R. M., 1880; 38379 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Bishop, William T., 1880, 1884; 38380 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Bissell, T.P., 1870; 38381 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Black, Chauncey F., 1868 - 1886; 38382 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Black, Jeremiah S., 1868 - 1883, n.d.; 38383 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Blain, William, 1868; 38384 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Blair, Franklin P., 1845, 1868 - 1870; 38385 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Blair, Montgomery, 1866 - 1883; 38386 (Box 6, Folder 38-40)
    - Blair, W.H., 1880; 38387 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Blanchard, Newton Crane, 1884; 38388 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Bland, B.F., 1876; 38389 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Blatchford, Samuel M., 1856 - 1862; 38390 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Bledsoe, William C., 1876; 38391 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Bleecker, Anthony, 1846 - 1871, 1883; 38392 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Bliss, Archibald M., 1876; 38393 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Blood, Isaiah, 1869; 38394 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Blyth, Francis J., 1877; 38395 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Boardman, Andrew, 1841; 38396 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Boas, H.K., 1859; 38397 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Boggs, William G., 1846; 38398 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Bogley, Lewis, 1867; 38399 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Boorman, J., 1846; 38400 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Booth, William A., 1875, 1879; 38401 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bossford, William, undated; 38402 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Bosworth, Joseph S., 1846; 38403 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Botta, V., 1859; 38404 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Boucicault, Dion, 1880; 38405 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Bourne, Theodore, 1876; 38406 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Boutwell, George S., 1872; 38407 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Bovee, Marvin H., 1876, 1882; 38408 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Bowden, Samuel, 1863; 38409 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Bowen, Adna, 1868; 38410 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Bowne, Samuel, 1885; 38411 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Boyle, Edward R., 1846; 38412 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Bradbury, A. W., 1875; 38413 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Bradbury, Bion, 1876 - 1883; 38414 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Bradbury, Elbridge, 1834; 38415 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Bradbury, James W., 1879; 38416 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Bradley, Alvin C., undated; 38417 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Bradley, George B., 1875, 1882; 38418 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Brady, John R., 1880; 38419 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Bragg, John, 1876; 38420 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Bramhall, Charles, 1831 - 1833; 38421 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Brawley, William H., 1876; 38422 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Breckenridge, William C., 1883; 38423 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Brennan, Thomas S., 1870; 38424 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Bright, R. J., 1874; 38425 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Bristol, Wheeler H., 1875; 38426 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Broadhead, James O., 1884 - 1886; 38427 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Bromley, B.O., Ca. 1865; 38428 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Brooks, Erastus, 1866 - 1868; 38429 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Brooks, James, 1862 - 1872; 38430 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Browere, A.D.O., 1880; 38431 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Brown, Charles P., 1844 - 1845, undated; 38432 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Brown, Julius, 1880 - 1884; 38433 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Brown, Thomas, 1879; 38434 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Brown, W. L., 1885; 38435 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Brown, William J., 1847; 38436 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Bruguiere Brothers, 1855; 38437 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Bryant, Andrew Jackson, 1875 - 1876, n.d.; 38438 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Bryant, Carolan O'Brien, 1875 - 1880; 38439 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Bryant, F. F., 1880; 38440 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Bryant, Julia, 1860, 1876; 38441 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Bryant, William Cullen, 1846 - 1878, 1885, n.d; 38442 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Buchanan, James, 1857; 38443 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Buchanan, R. D., 1882; 38444 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Buckalow, C.R., 1871; 38445 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Bucknor, C. B., 1859; 38446 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Burke, John M., 1875; 38447 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Burnett, Daniel, 1843; 38448 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Burnett, Ward B., 1874 - 1875; 38449 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Burr, Alfred Edmond, 1867 - 1868; 38450 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Burrill, John E., 1867; 38451 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Burrit, James P., 1856; 38452 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Burroughs, Peter F., 1846; 38453 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Burroughs (First name unknown), 1846; 38454 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Burt, Addison M., 1846; 38455 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Burt, John, 1878; 38456 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Burton, Charles, 1848; 38457 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Burwell, D., 1857, 1861; 38458 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Bush, William, 1876; 38459 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Bushnell, C. M., 1885; 38460 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Bushnell, C. S., 1872; 38461 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Butler, Benjamin F., 1838 - 1858, n.d.; 38462 (Box 7, Folder 66)
      Also includes notes from Mrs. B.F. Butler and their daughter, Harriet.
    - Butler, Charles P., 1859 - 1874, n.d.; 38463 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Butler, H., 1843 - 1846, 1860; 38464 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Butler, William Allen, 1843 - 1888, n.d.; 38465 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Butler, William S., 1886; 38466 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Butterfield, Daniel, 1866, 1868, 1875; 38467 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Butterworth, Samuel T., 1857, 1859; 38468 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Butts, Isaac, 1856 - 1857, 1868, 1874; 38469 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Cagger, Peter, 1848 - 1868, n.d.; 38470 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Cahill, John, 1879, 1883; 38471 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Caldwell, A. B., 1876; 38472 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Caldwell, Samuel D., 1886; 38473 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Calhoun, John C., 1841; 38474 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Call, Wilkinson, 1877; 38475 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Cambreling, Churchill C., 1848; 38476 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Cambreling, Stephen, 1846; 38477 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Camden, J. N., 1884; 38478 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Cameron, Simon, 1862, 1869; 38479 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Campbell, Colin E., 1880; 38480 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Campbell, D. Forbes, 1878, 1883; 38481 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Campbell, Edward, 1880; 38482 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Campbell, Freeman, 1846; 38483 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Campbell, George, 1860 - 1863; 38484 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Campbell, John L., 1876; 38485 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Campbell, Malcolm, 1859, 1874 - 1875; 38486 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Canda, Charles J., 1871 - 1886; 38487 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Capen, Nahum, 1871 - 1884; 38488 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Cardozo, Albert, 1869; 38489 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Carey, Charles, 1878; 38490 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Carlisle, John G., 1885 - 1886; 38491 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      See also: Coastal defense; John Newton, William Henry Jacques, Samuel Randall.
    - Carnegie, Andrew, 1872, 1885; 38492 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Carpenter, James, 1846; 38493 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Carpentier, J. S., 1853; 38494 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Carrigan, Andrew, 1846 - 1847; 38495 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Carroll, John Lee, 1868, 1876; 38496 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Carter, James C., 1875, 1885 - 1886; 38497 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Cary, Samuel F., 1880; 38498 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Cass, George W., 1860 - 1875, n.d.; 38499 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Casserley, Eugene, 1846, 1866 - 1877, n.d; 38500 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Cassidy, Clinton, 1855 - 1859; 38501 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Cassidy, William, 1847 - 1873, n.d.; 38502 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Chamberlin, William, 1853 - 1856; 38503 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Champlain, M.B., 1868 - 1871; 38504 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Chandler, Charles H., 1880; 38505 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Charlick, William H., 1859; 38506 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Chase, Nelson, 1846; 38507 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Chase, Franklin, 1850; 38508 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Chase, Salmon P., 1848; 38509 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Chester, Joseph L., 1873; 38510 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Childs, George Washington, 1876 - 1886; 38511 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Chilton, W. H., 1876; 38512 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Chittenden, S. E., 1882; 38513 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Choate, Joseph H., 1871; 38514 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Christie, David, 1861; 38515 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Church, Sanford E., 1860 - 1874; 38516 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Churchill, D. A., 1877; 38517 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Churchill, F. H., 1864; 38518 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Cisco, John Jay, 1864, 1868, 1875; 38519 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Clancy, John, 1860; 38520 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Clark, E., 1849; 38521 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Clendinen, George, 1880; 38522 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Clerke, Thomas W., 1846; 38523 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Cleveland, Brown & Co., 1869 - 1883; 38524 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Cleveland, Grover, 1885 - 1886; 38525 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Cleveland, O., 1876; 38526 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Clinton, George W., 1875; 38527 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Clinton, Henry L., 1873, 1876; 38528 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Closkey, L. W., 1886; 38529 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Cloyes, William O., 1880; 38530 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Clunie, Thomas J., 1885; 38531 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Clymer, E. M., 1864 - 1876; 38532 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Cobb, Howell, 1857; 38533 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Cochrane, John, 1860; 38534 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Cocke, William Archer, 1885; 38535 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Coe, George S., 1885; 38536 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Coe, N., 1846; 38537 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Coke, Richard, 1875; 38538 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Colby, Charles L., 1885; 38539 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Cole, Ashley W., 1879; 38540 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Cole, William, 1853; 38541 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Coleman, William A., 1843; 38542 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Colgate, James B., 1885; 38543 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Compton, John, 1845; 38544 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Compton, R.J., 1846; 38545 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Comstock, Calvert, 1860, 1875; 38546 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Comstock, Elon, 1862; 38547 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Comstock, George, 1869 - 1878; 38548 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Cone, David Dennison, 1885 - 1886; 38549 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Conger, A.B., 1846, 1857, 1868, 1875; 38550 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Conkling, F.A., 1875 - 1876, 1880; 38551 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Conkling, Roscoe, 1875; 38552 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Connolly, Richard B., 1872; 38553 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Conner, James, 1846; 38554 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Conner, William C., 1875; 38555 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      Announcing the arrest of William M. Tweed in France.
    - Continental Hotel, 1866; 38556 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Cook, Theodore P., 1875 - 1877; 38557 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Cooke (first name unknown), 1874; 38558 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Cooley, James Ewing, 1875; 38559 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Cooper, B. F., 1846; 38560 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Cooper, Edward, 1869 - 1876; 38561 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Cooper, Frank, 1885; 38562 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Cooper, Peter, 1857, 1865, 1867, 1875, 1881; 38563 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Cornell, Alonzo B., 1882 - 1883; 38564 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Cornell, Thomas B., 1864; 38565 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Corning, Erastus, 1863 - 1864, 1885; 38566 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Cornwall, George, 1846; 38567 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Cottman, Thomas, 1876; 38568 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Courtney, Samuel G., 1864 - 1868, 1871 - 1875; 38569 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Cowen, Patrick Henry, 1874 - 1875; 38570 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Cowing, J.A., 1879; 38571 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Cox, Samuel Sullivan, 1866, 1872 - 1876; 38572 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Cramer, William E., 1845; 38573 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Crapo, Samuel A., 1846; 38574 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Creamer, Thomas J., 1871; 38575 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Crittenden, Alonzo, 1843 - 1846, 1875; 38576 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Crittenden, Thomas L., 1884; 38577 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Croker, Richard, 1873; 38578 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Cromwell, H.A., 1855; 38579 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Crosby, John P., 1846; 38580 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Croswell, Edwin, 1837, 1846, 1864; 38581 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Crosswell, S., 1842, 1844; 38582 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Cullen, Edgar M., 1875; 38583 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Culver, D.E., 1880; 38584 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Cummings, George P., 1878; 38585 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Cunard Line, 1873; 38586 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Curran, John P., 1846; 38587 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Curtis, George Ticknor, 1863 - 1876; 38588 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Cutting, F. B. (Francis Brockholst), undated; 38589 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Cuyler, Theodore, 1871; 38590 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Daly, Charles P., 1842, 1865 - 1885; 38591 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Dana, Charles A., 1872 - 1886; 38592 (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
    - Dana, Willam B., 1871; 38593 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Davenport, John I., 1872; 38594 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Davezac, Auguste, 1851; 38595 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Davis, Emerson E., 1876; 38596 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Davis, George S., 1860; 38597 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Davis, George W., 1846; 38598 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Davis, Ira B., 1846; 38599 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Davis, J.C. Bancroft, 1868; 38600 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Davis, Noah, 1882; 38601 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Davis, R. D., 1841; 38602 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Davis, S. N., 1838; 38603 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Dawson, Henry B., 1882 - 1885; 38604 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Dayton, Charles, 1878; 38605 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Dean, G., 1856; 38606 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Dean, William, 1845; 38607 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Delafield, Lewis, 1874; 38608 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Delevan, Daniel E., 1861; 38609 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Delmar, Alexander, 1868; 38610 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Delta County, Michigan, 1877; 38611 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Depeyster, John Watts, 1875; 38612 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Dessar, Leo C., 1875; 38613 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Devlin, John E., 1846 - 1876, n.d.; 38614 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Dewitt, William C., 1875; 38615 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Dewolf, Delos, 1846 - 1871, n.d.; 38616 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Dickenson, Anna, 1883 - 1885; 38617 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Dickenson, Don M., 1876; 38618 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Di Cesnola, Luigi Palma, 1884; 38619 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Dillon, Sidney, 1878 - 1881; 38620 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Diossy, John T., 1846; 38621 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Ditmars, Abraham D., 1875; 38622 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Dix, John A., 1846 - 1876, n.d.; 38623 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Doane, William Crosswell, 1884; 38624 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Dobbin, George W., 1859, 1873; 38625 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Dodge, J. L., 1875; 38626 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Dodge, William Earle, 1975 - 1878; 38627 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Doheney, John, 1874; 38628 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Doolittle, E. A., 1834 - 1876; 38629 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Doolittle, James Rood, 1862 - 1882; 38630 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Doremus, Robert Ogden, 1858, 1875; 38631 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Dorr, J. O., 1845; 38632 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Dorsheimer, William, 1874 - 1884, n.d.; 38633 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Doubleday, A., 1832; 38634 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Douglas, E. A., 1853; 38635 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Douglas, John W., 1872; 38636 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Dowdall, W. T., 1885; 38637 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Downing, George T., 1885; 38638 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Dows, David, 1875 - 1886; 38639 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Doane, William C., 1886; 38640 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Drake, Thomas, 1856, 1871; 38641 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Driggs, Edmund, 1875; 38642 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Drummond, Thomas, 1862; 38643 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Duck, Martin, 1879; 38644 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Dudley, J. G., 1875; 38645 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Dufferns (first name unknown), 1878; 38646 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Duncan, William Butler, 1861 - 1874; 38647 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Dunlap, George L., 1866; 38648 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Dunlap, Thomas, 1876; 38649 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Dwight, J. W., 1873; 38650 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Dwight (first name unknown), undated; 38651 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Eames, C., 1848, 1860; 38652 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Eames, F., 1853 - 1871; 38653 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Earl, Robert, 1866 - 1875; 38654 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Eastman, Harvey G., 1873; 38655 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Eaton, Dorman B., 1873 - 1875; 38656 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Eaton, William W., 1874; 38657 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Eddison, Charles, 1880; 38658 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Edmonds, John W., 1832 - 1846; 1865 - 1872; 38659 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Edmonds, Laura, undated; 38660 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Edward, Henry P., 1846; 38661 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Edwards, B. S., 1863; 38662 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Edwards, Uriah, 1846; 38663 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Eggleston, George Cary, 1882; 38664 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Eighteenth Ward Democrats, 1856; 38665 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Eldridge, Titus B., 1858, 1875; 38666 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Elliott, A. B., 1876; 38667 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Ellis, Matthew H., 1875, 1885; 38668 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Eltinge, Norman, 1886; 38669 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Ely, Smith, 1868, 1875; 38670 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - English, James E., 1868, 1870; 38671 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - English, William H., 1876 - 1882; 38672 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Enos, Pascal P., 1862; 38673 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Errett, Russell, 1872; 38674 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Evarts, William M., 1873 - 1884; 38675 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Everett, Edward, 1860; 38676 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Evesson, Henry, 1843 - 1846; 38677 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Ewell, Richard Stoddert, 1868; 38678 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Ewen, John, 1846; 38679 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Ewing, Thomas, 1876 - 1884; 38680 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Exchange Hotel, 1848; 38681 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Fairchild, Charles, 1874 - 1877, 1886; 38682 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Fairchild, S.T., 1876; 38683 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Falck, L., 1866; 38684 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Fargo, William G., 1870; 38685 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Fassett, Mrs. C. Adile, 1878; 38686 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Fatman, Joseph, 1862; 38687 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Faulkner, J., 1875; 38688 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Faulkner, Lester B., 1870 - 1880; 38689 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Fay, Joseph Story, 1864; 38690 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Fenton, Myles, 1877; 38691 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Ferguson, John, 1861; 38692 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Ferguson, William, 1865; 38693 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Ferris, Isaac, 1867; 38694 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Field, Cyrus W., 1876 - 1879; 38695 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Field, David Dudley, 1846 - 1877, n.d.; 38696 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Field, Kate, 1877, 1885; 38697 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Field, Stephen, 1870, 1877; 38698 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Fields, Thomas C., 1866, 1868; 38699 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Fillmore, Millard, 1869; 38700 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Fish, Hamilton, 38701 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Fish, Henry L., 1874 - 1877; 38702 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Fish, J.D., 1866; 38703 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Fisher, W.R., 1860; 38704 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Flagg, Azariah C., 1840 - ca. 1855; 38705 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Fleet, Joshua, 1846; 38706 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Flint, Austin Jr., 1874 - 1878, n.d.; 38707 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Flower, R. P., 1866 - 1885; 38708 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Fodell, W. P., 1862; 38709 (Box 11, Folder 67)